Evil's Back. For More.
Jeepers Creepers: Reborn is a horror film directed by Timo Vuorensola.
Forced to travel to a horror festival with her boyfriend, a young woman begins
experiencing premonitions associated with the urban myth of The Creeper.
She believes that something supernatural has been summoned
— and that she is at the center of it all.
Laine, played by Sydney Craven.
Chase, played by Imran Adams.
The Creeper, played by Jarreau Benjamin.
Stu, played by Peter Brooke.
Carrie, played by Ocean Navarro.
Jamie, played by Matt Barkley.
Jeepers Creepers: Reborn is a 2022 supernatural horror film serving as a reboot of
the Jeepers Creepers film series and the fourth installment overall.
The film was directed by Timo Vuorensola, and written
by Jake Seal and Sean-Michael Argo.
Starring Sydney Craven, and Imran Adams, with "special appearances" from Dee Wallace and Gary Graham, it follows a young man and woman who
travel to a horror festival, with the latter becoming a target for a dark purpose by a reawakened creature called "the Creeper".
Jeepers Creepers: Reborn was released worldwide by Screen Media Films on September 19, 2022, and
was critically panned for its production values, lack of scares, and performances.
Additionally, the film became the subject of a lawsuit by Myriad Pictures, who claimed ownership of the
rights after producing the previous films, and were not notified of the film's production.
The tone is dark.